For UX and customer discovery, uh UX is
something that uh I discovered um a
while back, so more than 10 years back
as being the base for uh everything that
I do. So, I have the user in mind all of
the time. And so did the designer of
this table when um they built uh this
table for giraffes because otherwise, it
would hurt their neck to uh drink at the
cocktail bar that would be uh much
lower. So, this is actually UX and it is
not only based for software, AI, or
interaction, but also uh on physical um
on physical objects. And for customer
discovery,
we will talk a lot about interviews,
about discussing with users. This whole
deck and whole discussion is about the
fact that you need to get out of the
building and discuss with users. And I'm
going to teach you how to do that right
because also you can discuss uh with
users, say that you did, but uh if
you're not doing it right, then it's for
nothing.
So, [snorts]
um
you can see here uh an example uh of a
founder that goes and talks to uh his
pa- parents. And uh you'll find out that
this is not the way uh in which you
should do it because your parents will
always uh love your ideas because guess
what? They're your parents and they need
to love you and your ideas
uh the same.